adkarma.net 2015-04-05

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy pertains to the AdKarma website — www.adkarma.com — and is applicable to all
users that visit the site.
The website is used for providing business information to prospective clients and business partners. It
also serves as a marketing vehicle for AdKarma. AdKarma is committed to respecting your privacy and
conducting business matters that follow all policies as required by law. Please read the following policy
to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy is effective as of January 1,
2013, but may change periodically to reflect any changes in legal requirements, company procedures,
company products, service offerings and/or technology.
Collection of "PII" (Personally Identifiable Information)
Personally identifiable information is only collected when you choose to provide it to AdKarma, such as
in an email or by completing a form on the website. The site does contain a contact page where you can
contact AdKarma personnel and request additional information. This PII may include: name, company
name, address, telephone number or email address. This information is only used by AdKarma to
contact you in response to your inquiry, conduct business activities with you, provide customer service
and provide new products and services to existing and prospective customers. You can request the
individual information that AdKarma has collected about you, correct factual inaccuracies in
information, remove personal information and/or update your personal information by contacting
privacy@adkarma.com. While AdKarma may use the information it collects to notify you of necessary
changes to the website, new services/offerings and unique opportunities, you can contact AdKarma at
any time if you do not wish to receive these notices by emailing AdKarma at privacy@adkarma.com.
Third-party websites
AdKarma is not responsible for the methods by websites or applications that contain links on the
website or are linked to its website nor the contact and information presented therein. Third-party
Internet sites and services accessible through AdKarma have separate privacy and data collection
practices, independent of AdKarma. AdKarma has no responsibility or liability for these independent
policies or actions.
Disclosure/Sharing of "PII" (Personally Identifiable Information)
Disclosure of personal information is not shared with anyone outside of AdKarma, unless specifically
stated otherwise. AdKarma does not sell, rent or lease such personal information collected on the site to
non-affiliated third parties without your consent. If data is being collected and/or maintained by any
company other than AdKarma or an agent for AdKarma, you will be notified prior to the time of the data
collection or transfer.

AdKarma may share voluntarily-provided personally identifiable information (i) to enable third party
service providers to assist or facilitate in the services AdKarma provides; (ii) to comply with applicable
laws and regulations or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for
information AdKarma receives, whether or not a response is required by applicable law, and to
investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving
potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Access, or as otherwise
required by law; (iii) to enforce an agreement or to protect AdKarma's rights; with any parent, affiliated
or successor entity; (iv) in connection with any asset sale, transfer, divestiture or liquidation; (v) in
connection with strategic alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements to permit the offering
of products or services AdKarma believes may be of interest to you or where AdKarma has determined
that the information will be used in a responsible manner by the third party; or (vi) as permitted under
any agreement with you.
AdKarma may also share aggregated data with others. Aggregated data does not include personally
identifiable information. Except as provided AdKarma will not share any of your information with any
third party without your permission.
Collection of "Non-PII" (Non-Personally Identifiable Information) and Cookies
This website uses Google Analytics to help analyze how users use the site. The tool uses "cookies,"
which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor
behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use
of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate
visitors' use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for AdKarma.
We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect
any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP
address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP
address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with
any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information
via a fill-in form on our website.
Opt Out
If you do not want to store this information in your browser, you can easily deny, or opt out of, cookies.
There is more than one way to opt out of cookies: manually delete your cookies by following the
instructions contained in the "Help" section of your browser; or go to our ad server, ZEDO’s, opt-out
page: http://www.zedo.com/tools/zedo_optout.cgi. Click the "Opt Out Now" button provided. You can
also visit our video ad server, AdapTV’s, opt-out page: http://adap.tv/ and click Opt Out at the bottom of
the page. We will no longer deliver ads targeted to your preferences and usage patterns. The ZEDO and
AdapTV Opt-out Tools are cookie-based. In order for the Tool to work on your computer, your browser
must be set to accept third party cookies. If you buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete
this cookie, you will need to perform the opt-out task again.

We partner with ZEDO and AdapTV, third-party ad servers, and they are a member of the of the
Network Advertising Initiative (NAI), a cooperative of online marketing and analytics companies
committed to building consumer awareness and establishing responsible business and data
management practices and standards. The NAI provides a mechanism to opt out of its member
networks here: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp
Children Information
AdKarma is respectful and keenly aware of the privacy rights of children. AdKarma's products and
services are not intended for persons under 18 years of age and the website is not directed to children.
AdKarma does not knowingly solicit or collect any PII from children under the age of 18, nor knowingly
markets AdKarma products and services to children under this age. If you are a parent and are aware
that your child has provided AdKarma with PII without your knowledge or consent, please contact us
immediately at privacy@adkarma.com.
Security Measures
AdKarma uses appropriate measures to ensure the security of all information, including the use of
passwords, firewalls, encryption and remote servers, and routinely evaluates our practices to identify
security threats or opportunities for the improvement of our services. No transmission of information is
guaranteed to be completely secure. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other
factors may compromise data security. You acknowledge and agree to assume this risk when
communicating with us.
Other Notices
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time in the future. Please note that the use of
information that we gather is subject to the privacy notice in effect at the time of use.
Contact
If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy in connection with this policy, please send us a
thorough description to privacy@adkarma.com and we will try to resolve it. You may also contact us at
573-446-7366 or by mail at:
AdKarma
3806 Buttonwood Dr., Suite 101
Columbia, MO 65201
